大家好，我是强尼凯许
Hello, I'm Johnny Cash.
♪ 我听到火车开过来，轰隆轰隆地从拐弯角传来 ♪
♪ I hear the train a comin' It's rolling round the bend ♪
旗下公司
媒体
华纳
♪ 不记得什么时候起 就再没见过阳光 ♪
♪ And I ain't seen the sunshine Since I don't know when ♪
♪ 我被关在福尔松监狱 ♪
♪ I'm stuck in Folsom prison ♪
♪ 这里的时间真煎熬 ♪
♪ And time keeps draggin' on ♪
♪ 但是那火车 ♪
♪ But that train Keeps a rollin' ♪
♪ 一直奔着圣安东尼奥而去 ♪
♪ On down to San Antone ♪
♪ 当我是个孩子的时候 妈妈就告诉我，儿子啊 ♪
♪ When I was just a baby My mama told me, "Son" ♪
♪ 要做个乖宝宝 千万不要乱耍枪 ♪
♪ "Always be a good boy Don't ever play with guns" ♪
♪ 但我在里诺开枪打了人，看着他死掉 ♪
♪ But I shot a man in Reno Just to watch him die ♪
♪ 当我听见警笛鸣叫的时候 ♪
♪ When I hear That whistle blowin' ♪
♪ 捂着头不争气地哭了 ♪
♪ I hang my head and cry ♪
我还有15分钟的活动时间
I got another 15.
今天没了，你有事情做了
Not today, you don't. You're up.
你知道规矩
You know the deal.
成功完成任务
Successfully complete the mission,
就能减刑10年
you get ten years off your sentence.
若以任何方式违抗命令
You fail to follow my orders in any way
我就会引爆你脑袋里面的炸弹
and I detonate the explosive device
装备成功
好 狗腿子
Good dog.
我们是秘密行动小组
We are a black ops unit.
意思就是 你在这里见到的一切都从未发生过
Meaning, nothing you see here ever happened.
智者
Savant.
你的指挥官是瑞克·弗莱格上校
Your commanding officer
还是我叫你"德林"呢？
Or would you rather be called Durlin?
我更愿意你别叫我
I'd rather not be called at all.
但我会拼尽全力离开这个鬼地方
But I'll do anything to get out of this hellhole.
好吧 欢迎你来到“拼尽全力”的地方
Well, welcome to "anything."
所以这就是大名鼎鼎的自杀小队
So this is the famous Suicide Squad.
是的 不过那称呼有点贬义
Well, we consider that term degrading.
我们的官方名称是“X特遣队”
The official term is "Task Force X."
无论你喜不喜欢这些人
And love 'em or hate 'em,
他们在未来几天都是你的兄弟姐妹
these are your brothers and sisters for the next few days.
偶!
Oh!
嗷
Whoa.
回旋镖队长
Captain Boomerang.
(本名:乔治-迪格-哈克尼斯，来自澳洲，擅使回旋镖)
黑色守卫
Blackguard.
(本名:理察-赫兹，拥有高科技装甲的三流罪犯)
蒙戈
Mongal.
(本名:未知，星际暴君之女，外星军阀，具备超凡的速度与强大的力气)
标枪
Javelin.
(本名:未知，曾是德国运动员，体能强，擅使标枪)
TDK
T.D.K.
(断臂侠，本名:佛洛伊德“TDK”贝尔金，擅长拆解自己四肢)
黄鼬
Weasel.
(本名:约翰门罗，冷血教授，主要的武器:黄鼬服装上的利爪)
当然还有
And, of course...
嘿 伙计们 抱歉我迟到了 刚去上了个大号
Hey, guys, sorry I'm late. Had to go number two.
嗯 知道这个可真好
Hmm, good to know.
弗莱格
Flag.
哦 抱歉 过一下
Oh, sorry. Comin' through.
嘿 回旋镖
Hey, Boomer.
你又回监狱干什么 哈莉?
What are you doing back in prison, Harls?
我在银行突然路怒症发作
I got road rage. In a bank.
哦 真对不起 借过一下
-Oh. So sorry. Comin' through.
-抓过来 扣那里 不 -那里? 这里?
-Turn it around. There. No. -There? Here?
扣进去 你现在安全了
Put it in there. Now you're safe.
好吧
All right.
谢了 兄弟
Thanks, man.
准备起飞 出发
Prepare for liftoff. And away we go.
哈莉和断臂侠 -澳洲人
Harley and T.D.K... - Digger.
他俩之前合作过吗
...have they worked together before?
还没 我好激动
Not yet. I'm excited.
智者是干什么的来着?
What does Savant do again?
他叫布莱恩·德林
It's Brian Durlin.
他是武器与肉搏专家
He's an expert in weapons and hand-to-hand combat.
我赌二十块钱，他肯定会死
Yeah, well, I'm putting 20 on him that he's gonna bite it.
我也一样 接下来是黄鼬
Me too. And Weasel,
回旋镖队长和蒙戈  -我觉得
Boomer and Mongal. - Yeah, I think...
蒙戈是外星人吗 还是哪路神仙
Is Mongal an alien or some type of god?
你们在干什么 -嗨
What are you doing? -Oh. Hey.
就是在确保一切准备就绪
Just making sure everything was ready to go.
会议顺利，再会各位
Good meeting, everybody.
一个随意的例行晨会而已
Just our normal, casual morning meeting.
对 我正... 在做事
Yeah, I just gotta, uh, do this thing.
没什么好大惊小怪的
Nothing weird about it.
行  -好了
Okay. - Oh, yeah.
弗莱格
Flag.
在 我们再五分钟后降落
Yeah, we're T-minus five from the drop.
要保证整个小队
Get the whole team safely
安全抵达海滩 上校
to that beach, Colonel.
到达之后你将会收到新指令
You will receive further orders once there.
我们在屠夫的冷冻库里 哈莉
We're in a butcher's freezer, Harls,
旁边全像是挂在钩子上的死猪
surrounded by dead hogs hangin' on hooks.
只是他们没有自知之明
Only they don't know it yet.
别逗他了 回旋镖
Leave him alone, Boomer.
T.D.K. 是什么意思
What does T.D.K. stand for?
什么
What?
你不是叫T.D.K.吗
Your name is T.D.K., correct?
是啊
Yeah.
那代表什么?
And it stands for what?
代表我啊
It stands for me.
这不就是名字的用处
It's what a name is.
你的名字是字母组成的?
Your name is letters?
所有人的名字都是字母组成的 白痴
All names are letters, dickhead.
我喜欢你的口音
I love your accent.
美国女人都喜欢口音
American women all love accents.
确实 因为我们没有口音
We do. 'Cause we don't got none.
喂 这是条狗吗 -什么
Yo, is this a dog? -What?
这玩意儿是条狗吗
Is this thing a dog?
一... 一条狗 -嗯
A... A dog? -Yes.
兄弟 那你觉得这是什么狗
What kind of dog do you think it is, mate?
不知道 我又不是所有品种都熟悉
I don't know, I'm not familiar with all the breeds.
我觉得是阿富汗猎犬
I'm gonna go with Afghan Hound.
阿富汗猎犬什么时候长那吓人的手指了
Since when does an Afghan Hound have bloody thumbs?
天哪 它不会是狼人吧
Oh, my God, is it a werewolf?
我一直都希望能见到一个狼人
I've wanted to meet a werewolf forever.
他们居然让我坐在一个狼人旁边
Yo, they sat me next to a werewolf?
别乱动
That's not right.
快帮我解开 我可不想招惹狼人
Yo, let me out. I do not fuck with werewolves.
喂 喂 他不是狼人好吗
Hey, hey, he's not a werewolf, okay!
他是只黄鼬 人畜无害
He's a weasel. He's harmless.
也不是无害，有27个小孩死在他手上
I mean, he's not harmless, he's killed 27 children,
但我们需要他去...
but, you know, we got him to...
至少他和我们在同一艘船上
I think he's agreed to do this.
不管怎样
Whatever the case,
所有人准备降落
just everyone get into position to drop.
小丑去死
放纵 生活
没人确认过黄鼬会不会游泳吗?
Did anyone check on whether Weasel could swim?
黄鼬死了
The Weasel is dead!
重复 黄鼬死了
I repeat,the Weasel is dead. -
东北方向安全 可以靠岸
Northeast, all clear. Approach the shore.
完毕
Over.
智者 守在原地
Savant, hold your position.
收到
Roger that.
一群半吊子
Amateurs.
沃勒 我们上岸了 暂时安全
Waller, we're on the beach and dry.
黑色守卫!趴下，你...  -喂 兄弟们 喂
Blackguard. Get down, you... -Hey, guys! Hey.
...这里到处都是士兵!
...there's fucking soldiers everywhere!
你们可以出来了 是我
You can come out now, it's just me.
他到底在干啥
What the fuck is Blackguard doin'?
我是联系你们的人
I'm the one who contacted you.
这也在计划中吗? 什么情况?
Is this what's supposed to happen? What the fuck?
黑色守卫 回到你的位置
Blackguard, get back into your position.
看 我把所有人都带来了
Look, look. I brought everybody, look.
他们就在我后面
They're right behind me.
哇哦 喂
Whoa. Hey.
喂 兄弟们 哇
Hey, guys. Whoa.
我们不是说好了吗 额
We got a deal, right? Uh... Uh...
沃勒 我们暴露了
Waller, we're made.
是我联系的你们
I'm the one who called you.
黑色守卫出卖了我们
Blackguard sold us out.
他联系了该死的柯多马堤斯军队
He contacted the fucking Corto Maltese Army!
沃勒 我们得撤退
Waller, we need to retreat.
驳回 弗莱格
Negative, Flag.
这项任务非常重要
The mission is too important.
你们的成员很猛
This is a tough group.
你们可以的 -好吧
You can make it. -Okey-doke.
沃勒，恕我直言，我们被一群
Waller, with all due respect, we're in the middle
该死的... 哈莉 等等!
of a goddamn... Harley, wait!
哇哦!
Whoo-hoo!
0227的方向大门打开
Zero-two-two-seven is wide open.
上校 派出
Colonel, dispatch
断臂侠   -T.D.K.，两点钟方向
The Detachable Kid. -T.D.K., two o'clock!
T.D.K.意思是"断臂侠"?
T.D.K. is "The Detachable Kid"?
什么鬼
What the fuck?
这些队员都他妈不是我选的
I didn't pick the damn team!
别担心 弗莱格 直升机交给我
Don't worry, Flag, I got the bird.
蒙戈 别去
Mongal! Don't.
哎哟
Strewth!
回旋镖队长
Boomer!
智者吓跑了
Savant is off the rails.
智者 回来
Savant, turn back.
智者
Savant.
我警告你 你这是叛逃
Savant, I'm warning you, this is desertion.
智者
Savant!
最后一次机会 给我回去
This is your last chance. Turn back around.
你已经违反了我们的协议
You are in violation of your agreement!
噢 求求你 不
Oh, please! No.
该死
Damn it.
连滚导都知道
华纳兄弟=没有脑子
华纳兄弟影视公司出品
二队怎么样
How's Team Two holding up?
第一小队
第二小队
二队 情况汇报 定位点B
Team Two, check. Set point bravo.
阿特拉斯娱乐公司/
披得·萨夫兰
制片
南滩所有部队都已参战
All troops on the south beach are engaged.
二队已经在北滩就位待命
Team Two is clear to go on the north beach.
詹姆斯·古恩
电影
恭喜你 血腥运动
Congratulations, Bloodsport.
玛格特·罗比
饰 哈莉·奎茵
伊德里斯·艾尔巴
饰 血腥运动
约翰·塞纳
饰 和平使者
乔尔·金纳曼
饰 瑞克·弗莱格二世
你怎么做到的 沃勒?
How'd you do it, Waller?
配 鲨鱼王
西尔维斯特·史泰龙
以及
这里根本没有巡逻兵
There's no soldiers out here on patrol at all.
饰 阿曼达·沃勒
维奥拉·戴维斯
还有
他们要应付别的东西
Let's just say they were distracted.
X特遣队
全员集结
♪ Teddy去世时才12岁 ♪
♪ Teddy sniffing glue he was 12 years old ♪
饰 波点人
大卫·达斯马齐连
饰 二代捕鼠者
丹妮拉·曼希沃
♪ 在2:09分的时候从东边的屋顶摔下 ♪
♪ Fell from the roof on east two-nine ♪
迈克尔·鲁克
饰 学者
♪ Cathy离开的时候 只有11岁 ♪
♪ Cathy was 11 when she pulled the plug ♪
杰·科特尼
饰 回旋镖队长
♪ 她26岁时吃了很多安眠药 还喝了红酒 ♪
♪ On 26 reds and a bottle of wine ♪
饰 思考者
彼得·卡帕尔迪
♪ Bobby在14岁的时候 得了白血病 ♪
♪ Bobby got leukemia, 14 years old ♪
♪ 他去世的时候 看起来就像65岁 ♪
♪ He looked like 65 when he died ♪
饰 反抗军领导
艾莉丝·布拉加
♪ 他是我的朋友 ♪
♪ He was a friend of mine ♪
皮特·戴维森
饰 黑色守卫
♪ 那些人都去世了 ♪
♪ Those are people who died, died ♪
华金·科西奥
饰 苏亚雷斯将军
胡安·迭戈·博托
饰 半兽姐妹
♪ 那些人都去世了 ♪
♪ Those are people who died, died ♪
斯托姆·瑞德
饰 泰拉
内森·菲利安
饰 断臂小子
塔伊加·维迪提
饰 捕鼠者
♪ 那些人都去世了 ♪
♪ Those are people who died, died ♪
♪ 那些人都去世了 他们都是我的朋友 ♪
♪ They were all my friends, and they died ♪
饰 鲨鱼王
史蒂夫·阿吉
饰 黄鼬
肖恩·古恩
死亡
♪ G - Berg和乔吉对自己的病情不予理睬 ♪
♪ G-berg and georgie let their gimmicks go rotten ♪
选角
约翰·帕帕席德拉
♪ 于是他们在曼哈顿因肝炎去世 ♪
♪ So they died of hepatitis in upper manhattan ♪
服装设计
朱迪安娜
马科夫斯基
死亡
♪ Sly在越战中头部中弹 ♪
♪ Sly in vietnam took a bullet in the head ♪
凯尔文
麦克伊尔温
视觉特效
♪ 那晚Bobby结婚了 ♪
♪ Bobby od'd on drano on the night that he was wed ♪
电影作曲家
约翰·墨菲
♪ 他们是我的朋友 ♪
♪ They were two more friends of mine ♪
死亡
西蒙
哈特
拉斯·P·温特
监制
♪ 我很想念他们 但是他们都去世了 ♪
♪ I miss 'em--they died ♪
弗雷德·拉斯金
克里斯蒂安·瓦格纳
剪辑
♪ 那些人都去世了 ♪
♪ Those are people who died, died ♪
贝丝·米克尔
艺术指导
♪ 那些人都去世了 ♪
♪ Those are people who died, died ♪
危急
♪ 那些人都去世了 ♪
♪ Those are people who died, died ♪
摄影指导
亨利·布拉汉姆
♪ 我的那几个朋友都去世了 ♪
♪ Two more friends are died ♪
电影源自
漫画
死亡
制片人
扎克·施奈德
黛博拉·施奈德
沃尔特·浜田
翠怀恩•农
♪ Mary在酒店房间里跳楼了 ♪
♪ Mary took a dry dive from a hotel room ♪
♪ Bobby在坟墓般的监狱里上吊了 ♪
♪ Bobby hung himself from a cell in the tombs ♪
执行制片人
尼古拉斯·科达
萨克尔
♪ Judy卧轨自杀 ♪
♪ Judy jumped in front of a subway train ♪
死亡
查尔斯·罗文
制片人
♪ Eddie割破了自己的喉咙 ♪
♪ Eddie got slit in the jugular vein ♪
制片人
彼特·萨法兰
♪ eddie 我最想念你 ♪
♪ And eddie, I miss you more than all the others ♪
♪ 我的兄弟 我向你致敬 ♪
♪ And I salute you brother ♪
♪ 那些人都去世了 ♪
♪ Those are people who died, died ♪
编剧兼导演
詹姆斯·古恩
三天前
♪ 我还没准备好咆哮 ♪
♪ I was not ready for the roar ♪
♪ 我不愿意穿囚服 ♪
♪ I was so discontent to wear that heavy load ♪
♪ 于是我双膝跪地 ♪
♪ And so I got down on my knees ♪
♪ 在那愚蠢的祈祷下 ♪
♪ Beneath the sucker's prayer ♪
♪ 我以前会去那里 ♪
♪ I would go to there before ♪
♪ 我想爱一个人，但我不知道该怎么做 ♪
♪ I wanna love somebody but I don't know how ♪
♪ 我很孤独，这让我很沮丧 ♪
♪ And I've been so long lonely and it's getting me down ♪
噢
Oh.
给你 冠军
Here you go, champ.
让一下
Excuse me.
这他妈血腥运动是谁?
Who the fuck is Bloodsport?
罗伯特·迪布瓦
Robert DuBois.
世界级神枪手
A world-class marksman.
任何东西进他手里都能变致命武器
In his hands, anything is a deadly weapon.
他爸爸是雇佣兵
His father was a mercenary
从儿子出生的那一刻起就训练他杀人
who trained his son to kill from the moment he was born.
他进监狱是因为用氪石子弹
He's in prison for putting Superman in the ICU
把超人送进了重症监护室
with a kryptonite bullet.
迪布瓦   -我的答案还是一样
DuBois? -Same answer as the last time.
滚开
Piss off.
我是不会加入你的狗屁自杀小队的
I'm not joining your goddamn Suicide Squad.
到时候就知道了
We'll see.
你有访客
You have a visitor.
他们说你惹上麻烦了?
They said you got in trouble.
我偷了东西
I stole.
偷了什么
You stole what?
一块新表   -星形插销
A style watch. -A star latch?
一块手表 可以看电视的那种
A style watch. You can watch TV on it.
为什么要在手表上看电视
Why would you want to watch TV on your watch?
我不知道
I don't know.
下次你偷东西的时候
Next time you want to nick something,
要找个搭档
you take a partner,
可以帮你把风
and they can be your lookout.
这就是你的建议
That's your advice?
是啊
Yeah.
你真是个烂爸爸
You're a terrible father.
嘿 我本来也不想当爸爸
Hey, I didn't ask to be a father
这一点你已经表达得很清楚了
You make that perfectly clear.
是你妈搞得我措手不及
Your mother sprung that one on me.
她已经不在了
Well, she's not around anymore,
你可不可以别老提她
so you can lay off of her, okay?
我也不想提她
Oh, I tried to lay off her,
但她把亲子鉴定给扯出来了
but then she dragged out the paternity test.
操你妈!  -操你妈!
Fuck you! -No, fuck you!
操你妈!   -操你妈!
Fuck you! -Fuck you!
操你妈!  -操你妈!
Fuck you! -No, fuck you!
操你妈!
Fuck you!
你居然不在乎我偷东西
I can't believe you don't care that I stole,
只在乎我被抓了
only that I got caught!
我不仅在乎你被抓了
I don't only care that you got caught,
我更失望你居然是因为偷东西被抓
I care that you got caught for stealing
偷了个他妈的垃圾电视手表
something as stupid as a fucking TV watch!
它还有其他功能!
It does other things too!
他妈的你手机是不够用吗?
But nothing that your phone can't fucking do!
真是丢脸
It's embarrassing!
不 最让人丢脸的是
No, what's fucking embarrassing
我有你这样一个爸爸
is having you as my father.
好吧 泰拉 我说过
Yeah, well, I told you, Tyla,
从我进来的那一刻开始
when I came here that any goodness
我仅存的善良就被那老家伙给掐灭了
I ever had in me had been wrung out bare by my old man.
还有我说过，离开这里，做你自己的事
And I also told you to go out there and do your own thing
远离我
and stay far away
还有像我这样的人
from me or anyone like me, didn't I?
既然你我都清楚，我对你没有任何好处
So, why are you here when you and I both know
为何你还要来这里?
I have nothing good to offer you?
因为我开庭日快到了
Because my court date is coming up,
沃勒小姐说你可以帮我
and Miss Waller said maybe you could help me out.
为了逼我 领导那该死的任务
To get me to lead your shite fucking mission,
你不惜把我14岁的女儿送进监狱?
you're gonna send my 14-year-old daughter
不
No.
你女儿16岁了 迪布瓦
Your daughter is 16, DuBois.
真是个年度最佳老爸
You're a real father of the year.
好吧 你知道吗?泰拉也该长大了
Fine. You know what, Tyla needs to grow up anyway
该死的越来越像她老妈
'cause she's a little ditzy like her fucking mother.
让她在少管所关一年，没有问题
So, a year in juvie, no fucking problem.
不会关少管所，年满16岁要去路易斯安那州
Not juvie. Being 16 in the state of Louisiana
意味着在现在的情况下
means that under the right circumstances,
她会作为成年人接受审判
she could be tried as an adult.
而且如果被定罪
And, if convicted,
就会被送来这里的美梦监狱
could be sent right here to old Belle Reve.
在这里，很难想像你那脆弱的女儿
And in here, well, you never know what might happen
会发生什么事
to a frail young thing like that.
很遗撼的是
Shames me to say
所有美国的监狱当中
that we have the highest mortality rate
这里的死亡率最高
in the entire U.S. prison system.
哇 嘿 嘿 嘿
Whoa, hey, hey, hey!
你他妈竟然敢用我女儿威胁我!
You're threatening my fucking daughter!
我在保护这个国家
I'm protecting this country.
所有人退后  -沃勒女士 我
Everyone stand down. -Miss Waller, I...
退后
Stand down!
我原本不会采取如此极端的手段的
I wouldn't take such extreme measures...
你说极端 是 是有点极端
Oh, extreme? Oh, yeah, a little extreme.
...如果这次不是一件
...if this mission weren't more important
事关重大的任务
than you could possibly imagine.
去你妈的任务
Fuck your mission.
你受过军事训练
You have the military experience necessary,
你的心理测验也表明
and everything in your psychological profile tells me
你有资格成为一个领导者
you have what it takes to be a leader.
他妈的 我不是领导者
No, I'm no fucking leader!
那我会把你变成领导者
Then I'll make you one.
你要加入，还是置身事外?
Are you in or out?
很好，咱们去认识你的队员
Good. Let's meet your team.
快走  -离我远点 混蛋
Come on.  -Fuck me, man.
走
Let's go.
她真要杀死他的女儿吗?
She was gonna kill his kid?
小队的成员各个都是
Each member of the team is chosen
因为一件特殊能力而被选择
for his or her own completely unique set of abilities.
这是克里斯托弗·史密斯，代号和平使者
This is Christopher Smith, known as Peacemaker.
他手里任何东西都能变成致命武器
In his hands, anything is a deadly weapon.
他父亲是军人，打从小孩刚出生
His father was a soldier who trained his son
就开始教他如何杀人
how to kill from the moment he was born.
你在嘲讽我吗?    -什么?
Are you having a laugh? -What?
你刚说小队的成员
You just said each member of the team is chosen
各有一种特殊能力，但他的能力跟我一样啊
for their unique abilities. He does exactly what I do.
但是更好
But better.
我瞄中心可以百发百中
I always hit my targets dead center.
我射得更靠近中心
I hit them more in the center.
别硬拗，哪能比中心更中心
Well, you can't hit something more in a center.
我用更小的子弹 -啥?
I use smaller bullets. -What?
能穿过你的弹孔
They go inside your bullet holes
边都不会擦到
without even touching the side.
下一位，鲨鱼王
Next up is King Shark.
我操
Holy shit.
这他妈是什么?
What the fuck?
有人说纳努威
Some people claim
是古代鲨鱼神的后裔
that Nanaue is a descendant of an ancient shark god.
无论如何 他很强壮而且致命
Whatever the case, he's strong and deadly.
他会说话吗?
Does it talk?
书，读   -哇
Book read. -wow
书拿反了
Book's upside-down.
看到了吗? 拿着书在那装模做样
See that? It's pretending to read a book.
我，聪明，书，非常喜欢
So smart, me. Enjoy book so much.
小心点
Be a mite careful,
他越来越喜欢人肉了
as he's developed a taste for human meat.
哈？
Huh?
下一位是 克利欧·卡佐
Next, we have Cleo Cazo,
二代捕鼠者
Ratcatcher 2. -
安静点!
Settle down!
哎哟
Ooh.
啥 我们请不起一代捕鼠者吗?
What, we couldn't afford Ratcatcher 1?
已经死了，这是他女儿
He's dead. This is his daughter.
卡佐 要一起来吗
Cazo, will you be joining us?
我才刚醒
I just woke up.
我早上总不太清醒
I don't function well early in the morning.
真是万分抱歉扰你清梦
My deepest apologies for disturbing you.
没事的
Hmm, it's all right.
给我滚出来
Get your ass out here!
千禧世代呀
Millennials.
这不行
Oh, no way.
那东西绝不能一起来  -她能控制老鼠
That's not coming with us. -She controls rats.
我知道，我看出来了，这能力太恶心了
I know, I caught that. It's a disgusting superpower.
这位是塞巴斯蒂安 来打个招呼
This is Sebastian. Say hello, Sebastian.
我才不要和老鼠握手
I'm not shakin' the rat's hand.
最后一位是艾布纳·克利尔
And finally, we have Abner Krill.
他脖子上是什么
What's that 'round his neck?
是能量抑制器
A power dampener.
别名波点人
They call him the Polka Dot Man.
波点人
Polka Dot Man.
他能干啥 朝别人扔波点吗
What's he do, throw polka dots at people?
真的吗
He does.
他能扔波点
He throws polka dots at people.
你好呀 波点人
Hey, Polka Dot Man,
要不要来我孩子的生日趴表演啊!
I was hoping you'd entertain my kid's birthday party.
他妈个怂货!
You fucking pussy!
这能算士兵吗?
These are soldiers?
我们得演示一下
We need to debrief.
真该死
Fuck.
柯多 马堤斯
柯多马堤斯
Corto Maltese
一个南美洲岸外的小岛
is a small island nation off the coast of South America.
过去一百年
Over the past 100 years,
这个国家活在埃雷拉家族
the country has been ruled with an iron fist
柯多 马堤斯
的铁幕控制之下
by the Herrera family.
但一周前，这位
But, a week ago, this guy,
西尔维奥·卢纳将军 以及他的左膀右臂
General Silvio Luna, along with his right-hand man,
马特奥苏·亚雷斯大将军
Mayor General Mateo Suarez,
发动军事政变
took control of the Corto Maltese government
推翻了柯多马堤斯政府
in a violent military coup.
埃雷拉家族被当众吊死
The entire Herrera family were hanged in a public execution.
虽然美国不容忍
Although the United States did not condone
埃雷拉家族的极权统治
the excesses of the Herrera regime,
但他们至少不反美
they were non-antagonistic toward the U.S.
而卢纳则是激进反美派
Luna, however, is virulently anti-American.
所以你想让我们杀了卢纳
So, you want us to kill Luna?
不
No.
这是约顿海姆
This is Jotunheim.
约顿海姆
一个科研机构
A scientific experimentation facility
里头正在进行着"海星计划"
containing something known only as Project Starfish.
我们的情报显示
Our intelligence sources tell us
那个海星来自外星
that Starfish is extraterrestrial in origin.
如果留在卢纳政权手里
In the hands of the Luna regime,
它可能会给美国和世界带来动荡
it is potentially cataclysmic for Americans and the world.
你们的任务是渗透约顿海姆
Your mission is to infiltrate Jotunheim
销毁有关海星计划的一切
and destroy every trace of Project Starfish.
我们怎么进去
How are we supposed to get in?
"思考者"盖乌斯·格里夫斯
Gaius Grieves, the Thinker,
是负责海星计划的遗传学家
is a geneticist in charge of Project Starfish.
下班时间他经常去一个俱乐部
After hours, he hangs out at a gentlemen's club
叫做"善良小猫"
known as La Gatita Amable.
用一切手段让格里夫帮助你们
Get Grieves to help you by whatever means necessary
他能帮你们混进约顿海姆
and he can get you into Jotunheim.
有问题吗?
Any questions?
那是什么?
What is that?
那是一个高射投影仪
That is an overhead projector.
你还有在用它吗?
Do you ever use it anymore?
没有了
No, not really.
那为什么不把它扔了?
So, why don't you just throw it away?
和平使者
Peacemaker?
"海星"是"屁眼"的俗称
Starfish is a slang term for a butthole.
这两个之间或许有什么关联?
Think there's any connection?
没有
No.
No...
纳努威
Nanaue.
手
Hand.
是的，那是你的手，纳努威，非常好
Yes, that is your hand, Nanaue, very good.
要全军覆没了
We're all gonna die.
希望吧
I hope so.
噢，老天啊
Oh, for fuck's sake.
如今
总部，南方出现骚动
Control, we have a disturbance south of here.
只是个障眼法 血腥运动
It's just a diversion, Bloodsport.
好的 我们穿过雨林去海谷
All right, we cut through the jungle
城外没有封锁线吗
Don't they have blockades at the city limits?
听说有
That's the word.
我们怎么进去? 这里有只鲨鱼耶
How we getting in? Especially with Charlie the Tuna here.
我他妈怎么知道
How the hell am I supposed to know?
你是队长
You're the leader.
你得做决定啊
You're supposed to be decisive.
我决定让你去吃一大袋鸡巴
And I've decided that you should eat
你觉得怎么样?
a big bag of dicks, how's that?
你好滑稽 但如果这整个沙滩
You're being facetious, but if this whole beach
都堆满了鸡巴
was completely covered in dicks
有人告诉我为了和平
and somebody said I had to eat
我必须把它们全都吃了
every dick until the beach was clean for liberty,
我也会说没问题
I would say no problemo.
为什么会有人把鸡巴堆在沙滩上
Why would someone put penises all over the beach?
谁知道疯子是怎么想的
Who knows why madmen do what they do?
嗯 你知道我是怎么想的吗
Well, you know what I think?
我认为自由这东西
I think liberty is just your excuse
只是你用来胡作非为的借口罢了
to do whatever you want.
不管是吃下一海滩的鸡巴还是疯狂杀人
Whether that's to eat a beach full of dicks or killin' folk.
哦 是吗
Oh, yeah?
至少我不像你 为了钱杀人
At least I don't kill men for money like you.
啊 又开始了
Oh, here we go.
你的皮肤有点问题
There's something wrong with your skin.
只是皮疹而已
It's just a rash.
那是皮疹
That's a rash?
哦 不
Oh, no.
你...
You...
是唯一...
are the only one...
有资格拿我的标枪的人...
fit to carry my javelin.
拿给...
Carry it for...
拿给谁?
Carry it for who?
到底给谁?   拿给谁?
For what? What the heck?
我要为谁拿这个标枪?
Who am I supposed to carry it for?
不许动
否则你就死定了！
真是头疼
This is so frustratin'.
他刚刚要我为了某个理由
He just told me I have to carry this javelin
拿好标枪 但是没说到底是为了什么!
for a reason, but he didn't say why!
沃勒 沃勒 沃勒
Waller? Waller. Waller!
好了 我们就在这扎营
All right, we'll camp here,
明天我们就直接去城里
and tomorrow we'll go straight through to the city
在天黑之前到"善良小猫"
to get to La Gatita Amable by nightfall.
怎么了
What?
你到底睡得有多死
How deep of a sleeper are you?
我刚做了一个特别美妙的梦
I was having the most wonderful dream.
如果梦到鲨鱼王正要吃掉你
If it was you about to be eaten by King Shark,
说明你能通灵
then you're psychic.
我不相信他会做这种事
I don't believe he would do that.
他眼里是多么善良
He has very kind eyes.
饿
Hungry.
你个混蛋
You bastard!
好了 别弄这么多老鼠过来
All right, calm down with the rats!
什么   -我怕老鼠
What? -I have a thing with rats.
你怕老鼠？ -对
You have a thing with rats? -Yes.
你还和我在一个团队  -又不是我要求的
And you're on a team with me? -Not something I asked for!
嘿 你在笑什么?
What are you laughing at me for, man?
你他妈怎么只穿内裤
Why the fuck are you in your underwear?
紧身白内内？认真的？
Tighty-whities? Really?
哇 这话有点种族歧视了 -不
Now, that's just racist. - No.
不是种族歧视
It's not racist.
这就是紧身白内裤  -哦 他妈的不是吧
They're tighty-whities. - Oh, come the fuck on.
血腥运动有老鼠恐惧症
Bloodsport's got a rat phobia.
什么
What?
你没跟我说
You didn't tell me
你怕老鼠啊 迪布瓦
you had a fear of rats, DuBois?
我是个刺客 我为什么要暴露自己的弱点
I'm an assassin! Why would I share my liabilities?
妈的 笑死我了
For fuck's sake.
噢 它想送你一片漂亮的叶子
Aw. He's offering you a pretty leaf
来表示他没有恶意
to show you he means no harm.
我他妈的为什么会想要一片叶子
Why the fuck would I want a leaf?
快把老鼠弄走!
Just get the rats out of here!
噢 他妈的 -嗯哼 好了
Oh, fuck's sake. -Huh. Cool.
嘿，所以要干掉这大家伙吗 还是怎样?
Hey, we gonna kill Megalodouche now, or what?
纳努威是你们小队最厉害的成员
Nanaue's the strongest member of your team.
有他才能进入约顿海姆
You need him to get into Jotunheim.
如果我们需要时时刻刻警惕
Yeah, well, we can't function as a team
某个队员会把另个队员吞进肚子里的话
if we gotta watch our back
我们很难正常行动
from one of our own eatin' our bollocks.
纳努威 你会吃掉你的朋友吗?
Nanaue, would you eat your friends?
我，没，朋友
I no friends.
你没有朋友？
You have no friends?
如果你有的话 你会吃他们吗
If you did, would you eat them?
肯定会
Yes.
不会的吧？
No?
那 我们能成为朋友吗?
Then, can we be your friends?
得了吧
Come on.
他显然是在说谎
He's obviously lying.
如果我为爱赔掉性命
If I die 'cause I gambled on love,
那也值得了
it will be a worthy death.
朋友
Friends.
你可真是个小白痴
You are a little idiot.
啊 我的天呐 我的天呐 我真擅长这工作
Oh, my God! Oh, my God. I'm good at my job.
我找到他了
I found him.
快过来看
Check it out.
看 就在这儿 往北一英里的地方
Look, right here, a mile north.
X特遣队
Task Force X,
你们有一项额外的任务指令
you have an additional mission directive.
我们找到了瑞克·弗莱格上校的位置
We've located Colonel Rick Flag.
他被敌人带走了
He's been taken by the enemy.
瑞克·弗莱格?
Rick Flag?
我知道 你们俩曾在同个部队服役过
I know, you both served
在那个攻占阿夫拉尔·卡达姆的行动中
on special forces in Qurac that took down Avral Kaddam.
弗莱格是第一个推荐你的人
Flag was the one who initially recommended you.
你在柯多马堤斯安排了别的战斗小队
You had other operatives
却没有告诉我们?
and didn't tell us?
这个计划本来没有战术优势 但现在有了
There was no tactical advantage, now there is.
我已经把位置上传到了你们的通信器中
I've uploaded the location on your MTS.
把你们的愤怒发泄在抓走他的人身上吧
Terminate his captors with extreme prejudice.
记住 见一个杀一个 他们都是危险分子
Kill anyone you see. These are dangerous people.
进去约顿海姆前，得救回弗莱格
Recover Flag before moving on to the city.
那就是他们关押弗莱格的地方
That's where they're holding Flag.
美好的一天从酣畅淋漓的杀戮开始
Nothing like a bloodbath to start the day.
他们不是叫你和平使者么？
They call you Peacemaker?
我一心一意只为和平
I cherish peace with all my heart.
只要能达到这个目标 不论要杀多少人
I don't care how many men, women,
哪怕是女人和小孩 我都不在意
and children I need to kill to get it.
我还以为你才是脑子有问题的那个
I thought you were the crazy one.
我确实是
I am.
好了
All right.
准备开干
Let's get it.
再来一杯吗 老大
Boss.
谢了
Gracias.
不 不 不
No, no, no!
求求你不要
嗯
Hmm?
不是致命伤
Non-lethal.
你输了
You lose.
我打的是小型爆炸子弹
Exploding compression bullets.
最讨厌看人炫耀
No one likes a show-off.
除非那炫耀是真他妈酷
Unless what they're showing off is dope as fuck.
妈的 确实是这样
Fuck. That's true.
他还真是靠甩波点来杀人
He does throw polka dots at people.
我很抱歉 搞得这么浮夸
I'm sorry it's so... flamboyant.
我觉得很酷
It looks cool. I think.
我不喜欢随便杀人
I don't like to kill people,
但只要把他们想成是我母亲 我就能下手
but if I pretend they're my mom, it's easy.
消息量有点大 兄弟
T.M.I., mate.
迪布瓦?
DuBois?
嘿 弗莱格
Hey, Flag.
你怎么在这
What the hell are you doing here?
沃勒说你被
Waller told us that you were...
呃
Uh...
你们是在喝茶吗?
Are you drinkin' tea?
这是索尔·索里亚
This is Sol Soria,
她是自由军的领袖
she's the leader of the freedom fighters,
他们准备推翻现任政府
the resistance trying to take down the current government.
他们救了我一命
They saved my life.
哇哦
Oh, wow.
怎么你们都到这了 我的人还没发警报
Why did my people not alert me of your arrival?
我们路上没遇到人
We didn't see any people.
对的 半个人都没碰见
Yeah, I didn't see anybody on the way...
连个鬼影都没
There's no one out there.
来的时候他们已经走了
They were gone when we got here.
我把他们想象成母亲，然后杀了他们
I turned them into my mother in my head and killed them.
标准的美国人，肆意入侵，任性开枪
Typical Americans. Just run in, guns blazing.
我知道 被他们搞得天翻地覆
I know, this is messed up.
这些人 他们是...   -这玩意儿是干什么用的?
These guys, they're...   -What's this one do?
他们是一群蠢货
They're fucking idiots,
但现在我们双方的目标是一致的
but right now our objectives align with yours.
要是约顿海姆符合情报的描述
If Jotunheim contains the technology
确实掌握了那项技术
our intelligence says it does,
那它就可能被用在柯多马堤斯的人民身上
then it could be used on the people of Corto Maltese
美国人也难逃其害
as well as Americans.
所以我们需要你的帮助
That's why we need your help
潜入这座城市 这样才能阻止他们
to get into the city so we can stop 'em.
那只老鼠是在向我招手吗
Is that rat waving at me?
看起来是的
It appears it is.
为什么
Why?
我猜它是在向你表示友好
I'm gonna guess because it's friendly.
卢纳和苏亚雷斯杀害了我全家
Luna and Suarez murdered my entire family.
只要能阻止他们 让我和恶魔做交易都行
I'd make a deal with the Devil to stop them.
我会帮助你的人进入海谷
Your people will have our help getting to Valle Del Mar
逮捕这个盖乌斯·格里夫斯
to apprehend this Gaius Grieves.
你好
Hey.
这是什么?   -你杀死了我的员工!
What is this? -You slaughtered my staff!
他们是埃雷拉的手下
They were loyal to the Herreras.
你是为谁效力呢 思考者
Who are you loyal to, Thinker?
他们叫你思考者 是吗
They call you "Thinker" yes?
你脸上这些乱七八糟的东西能让你变得更聪明吗
All that shit in your face is to make your brain good?
是的 让我更聪明
Yes, makes my brain good.
你是在讽刺我吗?
Are you being sarcastic with me?
妈的
swearing in spanish
冷静 冷静
Hey! Hey.
我可以像对待你的员工一样对待你
I shall do to you as we did to your employees.
嘿 马特奥
Hey. Mateo!
别像个孩子似的
这到底是什么
What is this?
海星计划
Project Starfish.
是我过去30年
It's been the primary focus of my experiments here
最重要的实验
for the past 30 years.
看这些鲁莽的美国佬...
毫无防备地把这怪兽带上了飞机
这... 这是在做什么
Here. What... What is it doing here?
噢
Oh!
它正在生小孩
It is having little babies.
这不是它的幼崽
Not progeny,
而是它的衍生体
extensions of itself.
它们会占据宿主的身体
They take hosts,
然后这些宿主反过来成为它中央系统的一部分
and those hosts in turn become part of the central being.
它以宿主的意识为能源
It feeds on their consciousnesses.
变得更巨大 更强壮
Grows larger, more powerful.
所以
So...
海星计划现在在哪儿?
where is this Project Starfish now?
关于那个怪物的传言是真的
在美国释放这个怪物
它就会摧毁他们所有人
不 马特奥
有了这么危险的武器 世界才会认真看待我们
我们可以跻身“大联盟”了 马特奥
好主意 总统
Marvelous idea, Presidente.
但是 正如我所说
But as I've noted,
我已经研究了这只怪物30年
I've been working with the beast for 30 years.
除了我 没有谁有能力控制它
And there's no one but me capable of controlling it.
好吧 那么
Well, then...
欢迎你的加入
welcome to the team.
卡米拉
Si, Camila.
总统
Presidente.
您要找的囚犯
我们已经找到了
与此同时 哈莉
你们真是大错特错
You are making a big mistake
把我扔到这下面
throwing me down here!
我很快就会从这里出去
I will be outta here soon enough
到时候 我会杀掉你们每一个人
and I will kill every last one of you,
柯多马堤斯 马堤斯
Colto Maltese-tezios. Maltese-els.
马堤马堤人 柯多马 冒斯？
Malte-multoids. Colt-a-mults?
鬼知道你们这帮马力欧卡丁车蠢货叫什么
Whatever you Mario Kart-racing d-bags are called!
来
Please.
把这个穿上
Put this on.
天呐
Oh, wow.
我是个公主
I'm a princess.
奎茵女士
Senorita Quinn,
谨代表我们尊敬的西尔维奥·埃莱乌特里奥·卢纳总统
on behalf of the entire staff of Our Honorable General
及其所有下属人员
Presidente Silvio Eleuterio Luna,
很荣幸为您服务
it's a pleasure to serve you.
谢谢
Gracias.
妈妈让我倒着数一次
My mother said to count back again.
10 9
Ten, nine,
8 7 6
eight, seven, six,
5 4 3
five, four, three,
2 1 哈!上校 接招...
two, one. Ha! Coronel, beat that...
哦
Oh.
原谅我这样出场 奎茵女士
Forgive my appearance, Senorita Quinn.
多年来
I have admired you from afar
我一直仰慕着你
for many years now.
女士
Senorita.
你说我？
Me?
你是我的偶像 这里的人民也视你为英雄
You're a hero to me, as well as to my people.
你把我说迷糊了
I think you might got me confused.
哈莉奎茵在面对美国压迫时
Harley Quinn's fire and rebellion
表现出的激情和反抗精神
in the face of American oppression
是我们整个国家所追求的
is something to which my entire country aspires.
噢
Oh.
我准备了午餐
I have prepared lunch.
能否赏脸与我共用
Would you be so kind as to join me?
我很赏脸 当然可以
I'm so kind, sure.
♪ 如果你感觉孤单 ♪
♪ So if you're lonely ♪
♪ 为何不敢承认 ♪
♪ why'd you say your not lonely ♪
♪ 你是个单纯的傻姑娘 我听人说过 ♪
♪ Oh your a silly girl, I know I hurt it so ♪
♪ 如同你来了又离去 ♪
♪ It's just like you to come and go ♪
♪ 我知道也许你根本没有注意到我的存在 ♪
♪ And know me no you don't even know me ♪
♪ 你的甜美音容深深吸引我 ♪
♪ You'sre so sweet to try oh my you caught my eye ♪
♪ 你让我无法抗拒 ♪
♪ A girl like you's just irresistible ♪
♪ 如果你感觉孤单 ♪
♪ So if you're lonely ♪
♪ 为何不敢承认 ♪
♪ why'd you say your not lonely ♪
你要我干什么？
You want me to what?
嫁给我
To marry me.
你在开玩笑
You're joshing.
我能直说嘛 哈莉
Might I be frank, Harley?
你说吧
You might be.
好的 听着
Good, listen.
掌权后我得到了大部分人的支持
Since I took control, the majority love me.
但还是有些人
But some find me to be
无法接受我成为领袖
an unacceptable leader.
什么样的蠢货会这么觉得？
What kinds of dicks would find that?
难道他们不知道你有多优秀吗？
Don't they know how awesome you are?
你给他们看那些小鸟了吗？
Have you shown them the birdies?
可能对你们国家的人来说
It may sound archaic
这听起来很过时
to someone from your part of the world,
但是我的人民 柯多马堤斯人
but my people, the Corto Malteseans,
他们非常保守
they're very old-fashioned.
柯多马堤斯人 这么说才对
Corto Malteseans, of course.
而且我还是个单身汉
And I am a bachelor.
所以他们想让你找个老婆
So they want you to get hitched?
人们都说你是我妻子的完美人选
My people say you would make the perfect wife.
因为 你也知道的
Because, you know,
你能代表人民的反美情绪
you symbolize anti-American fervor.
是这样
Oh.
但我骨子里是个浪漫的人 哈莉
But I am a romantic, Harley.
虽然我当初答应见你只是为了安抚民众
I agreed to meet with you just to appease them.
但是 在见到你的那一天
However, upon spending the day with you,
我已经为你沦陷了
I find myself hardly able to think straight.
你的每一点都让我 你实在太性感了
-You are perfect in every... -You are so freaking hot.
♪ 如果你感觉孤单 ♪
♪ So if you're lonely ♪
♪ 为何不敢承认 ♪
♪ why'd you say your not lonely ♪
♪ 你的甜美音容深深吸引我 ♪
♪ You'sre so sweet to try oh my you caught my eye ♪
♪ 你让我无法抗拒 ♪
♪ A girl like you's just irresistible ♪
哈莉·卢纳
Harley Luna.
我喜欢这个名字
I like the ring of that.
那个就是约顿海姆吗
That's Jotunheim?
二战之后纳粹曾来这里寻求庇护
Nazis came here seeking asylum after World War II.
他们建了约顿海姆作为基地
They built Jotunheim to continue
来继续他们邪恶的实验
their unorthodox experiments.
后来埃雷拉家族接了对纳粹分子的通缉悬赏
Until the Herrera family accepted the bounty
把纳粹全杀了
and killed them all.
这么强
Wowza.
许多年以前 传说有一只怪物在帮助他们
Many years ago, the rumors began of a beast.
这些恐怖的传说帮助埃雷拉家族稳固了他们的统治
These dark rumors helped the Herrera family
他们会把政治对手
They would send their political enemies
和他们的家人送进一座堡垒
and their families to the fortress,
那些人再也没回来过
never to return.
我最近才知道
I have recently learned
这不是传说
these were not rumors.
他们在实验中利用这个诡异的生物
They were murdering thousands
害死了几千人
in bizarre experiments with this creature.
那现在你来接管它了
Well, it must be a big relief
就能松口气了吧
to got it in your hands now, huh?
没错
Absolutely.
现在该是让我们的敌人颤抖的时候了
Now, it is our enemies who shall be fearful.
要是任何人
If anyone dares to say a negative word
敢说他们现任总统一句坏话
about their new president today,
他们的父母 孩子 和所有深爱的人
their parents, their children, and anyone they ever loved
都会被送去约顿海姆喂怪物
will be sent to Jotunheim to feed the beast.
对不起了
I'm sorry.
就在最近 我对自己发誓
Recently, I made a promise to myself
下次我再交男朋友的时候
that the next time I got a boyfriend,
一定要警惕他身上有没有什么不对劲的地方
I'd be on the lookout for red flags.
要是有的话
And if I saw any,
我会替天行道
I would do the healthy thing
动手杀了他
and I would murder him.
你刚刚说杀害孩子
And killing kids?
就算不对劲了
Kind of a red flag.
我知道 我知道
I know, I know.
我知道你要说
I know what you're tryin' to say.
哈莉 为什么不直接离开我
"Harley, why not just leave?"
然后我会说 ‘为什么你要冲我大喊大叫’
And I'd say, "Why are you screaming at me?
‘我又不聋 我就站在这儿呢’
"I'm not deaf. I'm standing right here."
之后我还会说
And then I'd say,
‘当你选男人的眼光和我一样差时 你会发现’
"When your taste in men is as bad as mine,
‘他们不会悄悄在你的生活中消失’
they don't just go away quietly.
反而会扎爆你的轮胎 杀掉你的宠物狗
"They slash your tires and they kill your dogs and
甚至还会明目张胆地告诉你 你喜欢的音乐
tell you that the music you like
根本算不上真正的音乐
ain't real music at all."
然后这些残忍的言行
And all the cruelty...
会把你的心撕碎
...tears you apart after a while.
你真的是一个非常好看的人
You were real pretty and all,
愿你两腿之间的猛兽
and R.I.P. to that absolutely beautiful monster
也得到安息 但是
between your legs, but...
总体来说
all in all...
我认为你现在这样更好看
I think you're more pretty like this,
现在所有的糟粕思想都离开了你的脑袋
with all those rotten thoughts emptied from your head.
我简直不敢相信这玩意儿还有子弹
I can't believe this thing had a bullet.
举起手来!
好好好 我知道了
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got it.
将军们都同意了
让您继任总统 将军
我怀疑除了反对势力之外
不会有其他阻力了
西尔维奥对我来说就像兄弟
但他一直是个浪漫主义者
他希望全世界都能认真看待他
与此同时 他还养了一屋小鸟
俄国 美国 中国 --
除非怪兽摧毁他们
否则不会认真看待我们
苏亚雷斯总统
我们怎么处置哈莉·奎因？
我会从她那里榨取信息
但我怀疑美国人不止派了她一人
搜寻城内所有的美国人
然后 --
把自杀小队的人头给我拿来
你到底在干嘛？
What the hell are you doin'?
上校 我们累了 我们需要休息
We're tired, Colonel. We need a rest.
你们太菜了
Goddamn hobbyists.
我们不能停下来
We cannot stop.
如果你们要救我的人民 就要快一点
We need to hurry if you're going to help my people.
嘿 我们的目的不是为了救你的人民
Hey. We're not here to help your people.
不过她是对的 我们得继续赶路
But she's right, we gotta keep moving.
我 背着 朋友？
I carry friend?
没事的，纳努威
It's okay, Nanaue.
他的脸又这样了
It's happening to his face again.
没事的，我就是滑了一下  -喂
It's nothing, I slipped. -Hey...
诺曼·贝茨，我们有权知道这玩意儿会不会传染
Norman Bates, if that shit's contagious, we need to know.
不传染
It's not.
这是什么?  -这是一种
What is it? -It's a...
一种多维度病毒
It's an interdimensional virus.
那又是什么鬼东西？
Fuck is that?
我妈曾经是S.T.A.R.实验室的科学家
My mother was a scientist at S.T.A.R. Labs,
她非常痴迷于把我和
and she was obsessed with turning me
我的兄弟姐妹们变成超级英雄
and my brothers and sisters into superheroes.
她让我感染了
She infected me.
现在 我每天必须排出两次波点 否则
Now, if I don't, you know, expel the dots twice a day...
会怎么样？
Then what?
它们就会生吞了我
They'll eat me alive.
那你的兄弟姐妹们怎么样了？
What happened to your brothers and sisters?
有些活下来了
Some lived.
有一些
Some...
死了
died.
那你母亲 她现在在哪？
And your mom, where is she now?
无处不在
Everywhere.
好了 咱们离开这里吧
Okay. Let's move out.
来吧 我们得赶快
Come on, we must hurry,
不然就要错过和联系人约定的时间了
or we'll be late to meet my contact.
♪ 我听见那个人在说着什么 ♪
♪ I heard the men saying something ♪
♪ 船长说他们给了你丰厚的酬劳 ♪
♪ The captains tell they pay you well ♪
♪ 他们说他们需要船员 ♪
♪ And they say they need sailing men to ♪
♪ 来为他们带路 在今天带他们离开 ♪
♪ Show the way and leave today ♪
♪ 是你问 ♪
♪ Was it you that said ♪
♪ 需要多久 ♪
♪ How long how long ♪
出示你的许可证
好的 等一下
你在找什么人吗？
没有，我只是...
给我一秒钟...
你是从哪来的？
我该怎么解释呢 我...
再等一下...
让我看看...
开门快点!
你那里有什么东西？
下车快点! 现在！
拜托让我..
好吃 好吃
Nom，nom！
你是弥尔顿吗
Are you Milton?
对
Si.
弥尔顿会开车带你们穿过小镇
Milton will drive you through town
去到善良小猫酒吧
and to La Gatita Amable.
箱子里是给你们的衣服
There are clothes in the boxes for all of you
换装之后混进去
so you can blend in.
不过 行走的鲨鱼目标太大
That said, the walking tiburon
必须藏起来
is gonna have to stay out of sight.
我会乔装打扮
I wear disguise.
天呐 你要乔装打扮了
Oh, you're going to wear a disguise.
是的
Si.
嘿 他在学西班牙语
Hey, he's learnin' Spanish.
是什么样的伪装呢
And what kind of disguise?
假胡子 哦
-Fake mustache. -Oh.
假胡子没用的 伙计
Yeah, fake mustache isn't gonna cut it, mate.
肯定会有很多士兵看守约顿海姆
There's gonna be a lot of soldiers watching Jotunheim.
要是他们发现我们
If they discover us there...
那就祈祷他们不会 要不然你们都死定了
Let's pray they do not, or you will all be dead.
如果他们发现了
If they do,
那么那个宫殿就岌岌可危了
that'll leave the palace vulnerable.
卢纳和其他将军
Luna and the other generals
会失去保护
will be left without protection.
你是个好人 弗莱格上校
You're a good man, Colonel Flag.
你和原来没什么两样
You still look exactly like yourself.
这真是我见过最糟的假胡子
That's the worst fake mustache I've ever seen.
你要是敢糊弄 我们一定会杀了你
And if you had fooled us, we'd have to kill you,
长着小胡子的鲨鱼人
shark-shaped bloke with a moustache
像那样悄悄靠近我们
creeping up on us like that.
操
Fuck
你们 你们
You, you.
他老是想亲近你
He always wants to be near you.
我觉得他对你有好感
I think he senses good in you.
我可没什么好的
Yeah, there's no good in me.
该死
Damn.
还想这周末和参议员克雷一起打高尔夫
Supposed to play golf with Senator Cray this weekend.
我肯定会像个蠢货
-I'm gonna look a fool. -
沃勒 进来
Waller, come in.
啊
Ugh.
你没打进
You missed.
沃勒 听到了吗
Waller, do you copy?
信号开始不稳定了
We're losing connection.
♪ 你不应该说你爱我 ♪
♪ Te conviene no decirme que me quieres ♪
沃勒
Waller.
该死的
Fuck's sake.
♪ 我宁愿你走开 ♪
♪ Prefiero que te alejes ♪
X特遣队 沃勒
Task Force X. -Waller.
你们在吗
You there?
♪ 宁愿你留我独自一人 ♪
♪ Prefiero que me dejas sola ♪
军方肯定在
The military must have put
城市的各个角落放置了信号干扰器
signal jammers around the city.
即便通信中断
Your comms are down,
我们仍然可以激活炸弹
but we can still activate the bombs,
更不用说你女儿会怎么样了
not to mention what will happen to your daughter.
所以 别不老实
So, no funny business.
♪ 还有许多人令我失望 ♪
♪ Y me fallan tantas otras ♪
收到了吗 迪布瓦
Do you copy, DuBois?
收到
Copy.
操你妈的
Fuck you!
♪ 我永远无法取悦你 ♪
♪ Nunca te podría complacer ♪
那些关于他女儿的事
Hey, uh, all that stuff about his daughter,
你不会真要做吧
you wouldn't really do that, right?
你根本不知道我会做什么 约翰
You don't know half of what I would do, John.
♪ 我不是那种 ♪
♪ Yo no soy el tipo de mujer ♪
♪ 你妈妈希望和你在一起的女人 ♪
♪ Con quien tu mamá te quiere ver ♪
♪ 我欲望强烈 ♪
♪ Me hacen falta tantas cosas ♪
♪ 还有许多人令我失望 ♪
♪ Y me fallan tantas otras ♪
♪ 我永远无法取悦你 ♪
♪ Nunca te podría complacer ♪
♪ 她们忠诚 ♪
♪ Ellas son fieles ♪
怎么了
What?
♪ 她们圣洁 ♪
♪ Ellas son santas ♪
你为什么这么怕老鼠
Why are you so afraid of rats?
♪ 她们宽容，默默原谅你 ♪
♪ Ellas son buenas perdonan calladas ♪
那你为什么这么喜欢它们呢
Why are you so in love with them, Ratcatcher 2?
你知道我是怎么想的吗
You know what I think?
我认为你有严重的恋父情结
I think you have a serious case of daddy issues.
我可没有到恋父情结的地步
I have no issues with how much I loved my father.
虽然他是个天才
Although he was a genius...
但我们在葡萄牙流离失所 都是因为他的
we lived homeless in the streets of Portugal
负担
burdens.
他制造了我今天使用的机器
He built the machines I employ today...
还教会了我召唤老鼠的诀窍
...and taught me the secrets of calling the rats.
它们带给了我们维生的小首饰
They brought us trinkets to live on.
夜里 当我们要被冻僵的时候
And they kept us warm at night,
它们给了我们温暖
when we would have frozen.
但最终...   -爸爸
But eventually... - Papa.
爸爸 醒醒
Papa, wake up.
...我父亲的负担
...my father's burdens
变得太难以承受
became too heavy to carry.
不要
No.
不要 爸爸
No, Papa.
他就这样走了   -爸爸 醒醒
And he was gone. -Papa, wake up.
我带着他的机器来到美国
I took his machinery and came to America.
这就是所谓的梦想 不是吗
That is the dream, right?
但是我被捕了
But I was arrested
因为持枪抢劫银行 你敢信吗
for armed bank robbery, do you believe it?
政府认为老鼠是一种武器
The state considered the rats a weapon.
怎么了
What?
你让我想起了我女儿
You remind me of my daughter,
我来这里的原因
the reason I'm here.
你为什么这么怕老鼠
Why are you so afraid of rats?
我的长辈
My old man.
在我小时候
When I was a lad,
如果我没有顺利完成任务
if I didn't finish a task right,
他就会惩罚我
he would dole out the punishment.
有一次 他把我关在箱子里整整一天
And one day, he just locked me in a crate for 24 hours.
里面放满了饥肠辘辘的老鼠
And it was full of starvin' rats.
和我父亲一样有瑕疵
As imperfect my father was...
他爱我
he loved me.
我希望你也能感同身受
I wish I could give that to you.
你不必担心 知道吗
Don't you worry, yeah?
我要带你活着离开这儿
I'm gonna get you out of here alive.
是我要带你活着离开这儿
I'm going to get you out of here alive.
先生们 我们到了
Senores, this is the place.
♪ 也许，我已经朝着（心灵的）南方滑回 ♪
♪ Maybe I've been slipping back, heading south ♪
♪ 星期二，晕车 ♪
♪ Carsick on a Tuesday ♪
♪（又）丢了现金，只好停下（在中途下车）♪
♪ Missing cash, blacking out ♪
♪ 几种无情的际遇（同时到来）♪
♪ Heartless in a few ways ♪
♪ 肘部也受伤了，何谈幸运 ♪
♪ shit for luck, elbows shredded ♪
♪（或许是）我把事情稳定得太迟 ♪
♪ I held things steady like too late ♪
所以 这个思考者什么时候才来
So, when's this Thinker guy supposed to be here?
应该在几个小时之内就到了
Supposed to be in the next few hours.
貌似我们得找些事做
Looks like we gotta find something to do
来打发时间 嘿 服务员
to pass the time. Uh, miss?
要不来些 嗯
How about some, uh...
你们这边人经常喝什么 菲奈特苦酒
What do you guys drink around here, Fernet?
那就来一瓶菲奈特苦酒
How about a round of Fernets for the table.
好吗 好的
-Comprende? -Si.
嘿 造尿人 我们在执行任务
Hey, Pissmaker, we're on a mission.
放轻松 神探杰加特
Easy, Inspector Gadget.
小酌一下又没什么关系
A little drink never hurt nobody.
除了每年有数千人
Except for the thousands of people
都死于酒驾事故
killed in drunk driving accidents every year.
别扫兴 迪布瓦 这可能是咱俩最后一杯酒了
Come on, DuBois, this could be our last drink.
请享用
Gracias.
就喝这一杯
Just one.
你要做那种人吗   -我就是要做那种人
You're gonna be that guy? -I'm gonna be that guy.
嘿 小姐
Hey, chica.
别管那只老鼠
Forgot the rat.
敬咱们在三小时内还能活着
Here's to being alive in three hours.
我肯定会活着的 你祈祷你自己吧
I'll be alive. You speak for yourself.
瞧瞧你 瞧瞧你这样子
There you go, there you go.
不要再给波点人酒了
Don't give any more to Polka!
♪ 我无法入睡，我希望我保持清醒 ♪
♪ I can't sleep, I hope I stay awake ♪
♪ 因为我整日不停奔跑 ♪
♪ Cause I've been running, running, running all day ♪
♪ 慢慢长夜 没有一丝安宁 ♪
♪ Long nights, no peace ♪
♪ 我感觉每个人都凝视着我 ♪
♪ I feel like everybody's eyes on me ♪
♪ 我无法入眠，希望自己能保持清醒 ♪
♪ I can't sleep, I hope I stay awake ♪
♪ 因为我整日不停奔跑 ♪
♪ Cause I've been running, running, running all day ♪
♪ 慢慢长夜 没有一丝安宁 ♪
♪ Long nights, no peace ♪
♪ 我感觉每个人都凝视着我 ♪
♪ I feel like everybody's eyes on me ♪
♪ 我无法入睡 ♪
♪ I can't sleep ♪
全面搜查
谁也别信
美国人可能会在任何地方
让我进去！
少来这套 哥们！
走 往那走
Go. Go.
这是把真枪
That is a gun.
所以 保持微笑
So, smile.
我们是要去约顿海姆的几个老伙计
We're old mates who are gonna take a trip to Jotunheim.
没错
Yup.
即便有我帮忙 你们以为就能进得去？
Even with my help, you think you can get into Jotunheim?
好吧 如果我们进不去 外面还有一条大白鲨
Well, if we can't, I've got a Great White
在觅食
out back that's looking for some chum.
现在 跟我走
Now, come on.
就这样 慢慢来
All right, nice and easy.
哦 操
Oh, fuck.
朋友们
别担心
我们今晚只在这找美国人
希望没有影响到你们今晚的心情
但你们必须得出示身份证
士兵们！
出示你的证件...
快！
不 不要
No, no, no!
好吧
All right...
把他从后门带出去 懂吗
Take him out through the back, all right.
在平板上找到我的坐标 半小时后来找我
Find my coordinates in the pad and meet me in half an hour.
什么?    -嘿 你听懂我说什么了吗
What? -Hey, did you hear what I said?
听懂了，但是...   -快走
Yes, but... -Go.
我们走
Let's go.
嘿 别冲动
Hey, calm down.
没必要打扰大家美好的夜晚
There's no need to disturb everyone's night.
我就在这 我就是你们要找的人
I'm right here, I'm the one you're looking for.
对，我们也是 我们是他的美国同伙
Yep, us too. We're his American companions.
什么？
What?
噢
Ow!
走 快走    -他
Come on. Go. - He...
天呐
Oh, God.
走
Move it!
跟上
Come on!
嘿
Hey!
你的设备
Your equipment
控制动物的行为 那很聪明
manipulates animal behavior, clever.
我正在人类身上做类似的实验
I'm working on something similar with humans.
麻烦你安静点
Be quiet, please.
你显然慌了
You are perceivably panicked.
我猜你不是这个队伍的领袖
I'm guessing that you are not the alphas of this battalion.
你想试试十几只老鼠在你身体上爬的感觉吗？
Do you want a dozen angry rodents crawling up your ass?
我的回答可能不是你想要的
My answer might not be what you expect.
走 跟上!
Go, go!
♪ 有时我不介意细雨淅沥 ♪
♪ I do not mind the rain sometimes ♪
♪ 因为得到雨水滋润 玫瑰才会绽放生命 ♪
♪ Cause that's the only way the roses bloom ♪
不好意思
I'm sorry for you.
但是你们马上就会
But soon you will all be joining
跟你们那神经质的同伴哈莉奎茵汇合了
your deranged compatriot, Harley Quinn.
哈莉还活着？
Is Harley alive?
活不了多久了
Not for long.
马特奥·苏亚雷斯大将军在获取情报的时候
Mayor General Suarez can be rather harsh
可是会相当粗鲁
when extracting information.
点脉
Dim mak.
什么？
这是广东话的说法
That's the Cantonese term for it.
在日语里是急所术
In Japan, it's kyoshu jitsu.
英文里叫死亡之触
In English, it's simply the Death Touch,
如何一招杀人
how to kill a man with a single blow.
当然 一招杀人
Of course it's possible
是有可能的
to kill a man with a single blow.
但是这得看运气
But it's a matter of chance,
你没办法确保出手必制胜
and cannot be wielded with certainty.
这是他们的说法 他们？
-That's what they say. -They?
业余的 数到一？
-Amateurs. -On one?
一
One.
我不抽烟
I don't smoke.
♪ 有时我不介意细雨淅沥 ♪
♪ I do not mind the rain sometimes ♪
卧槽
exclaims in spanish
好了
All right.
我们出发去约顿海姆
Let's go to Jotunheim.
约顿海姆行动
不
Nope.
我们还有点事要处理
There's somethin' we gotta take care of first.
什么？
What?
约顿：
哈莉计划
♪ 我周围无人 ♪
♪ I ain't got nobody  ♪
♪ 无人在意我 无... ♪
♪ Nobody cares for me No... ♪
我再问一遍
I will ask again.
你有多少超能力队友
How many meta-power teammates
跟你一起来了柯多马堤斯？
arrived with you to Corto Maltese?
六十九个
Sixty-nine.
六十九个？
Sixty-nine?
你们是怎样把这六十九个队员送进...
How could you get 69 troops into the...
♪ 无如此悲伤且孤独 ♪
♪ I'm so sad and lonely ♪
♪ 妈妈会不会来救我... ♪
♪ Won't some sweet momma Come and rescue me... ♪
你在开什么玩笑
You gotta be kiddin' me.
你在冒着整个任务失败的风险
You're gonna risk the entire mission
只为了救一个精神有缺陷的宫廷小丑
for a mental defective dressed as a court jester.
这个主意还是一个头戴马桶座圈的家伙想出来的
This coming from a guy that wears a toilet seat
我们不会抛弃任何队友
We don't leave one of our own behind.
你能接受?
You're okay with this?
不 但我从弗莱格还带着口水兜的时候就认识他了
No, but I've been around Flag when he's got a rag
你最好别提这个  -你个混蛋!
Best not to tug it. -Motherfucker!
喂 醒醒 醒醒
Hey, wake up, wake up.
好了 我们出发吧
All right, let's go.
好 我们准备从三楼进去
All right, we'll enter through the third floor,
走内部楼梯 然后下去到地窖
go to the inner staircase, and then down to the cellar
也就是他们通常关押人的地方
where they usually keep their detainees.
但愿 哈莉还活着
Hopefully, Harley's still alive.
这不是一个马桶座圈 这是一个像征自由的信标
It's not a toilet seat, it's a beacon of freedom!
等她恢复了知觉再告诉我
让我们看看
切掉她的手指是否能唤起她的记忆
♪ 我只是小白脸无论我走到哪里 ♪
♪ I'm just a gigolo and everywhere I go♪
♪ 大家都知道我的角色 ♪
♪ People know the part I'm playing ♪
♪ 为每一场舞蹈付出代价贩卖每一份浪漫 ♪
♪ Paid for every dancce selling each romance ♪
♪ 噢 他们在说什么 ♪
♪ Oh what they're saying ♪
♪ 总有一天 ♪
♪ There will come a day ♪
♪ 青春终将逝去 ♪
♪ When youth will pass away ♪
♪ 他们会怎么说我 ♪
♪ What will they say about me ♪
♪ 当末日来临 ♪
♪ When the end comes I know ♪
♪ 我知道世上只有小白脸 ♪
♪ I know They'll say ''just a gigolo" ♪
♪ 没有我的生活还在继续 ♪
♪ As life goes on without me ♪
♪ 我走到哪里都是个小白脸 ♪
♪ I'm just a gigolo everywhere I go ♪
♪ 大家都知道我的角色 ♪
♪ People know the part I'm playing ♪
♪ 为每一场舞 蹈付出代价贩卖每一份浪漫 ♪
♪ Paid for every dance Selling each romance ♪
♪ 噢 他们在说什么 ♪
♪ Oh what they're saying ♪
♪ 总有一天 ♪
♪ And there will come a day ♪
♪ 青春终将逝去 ♪
♪ Youth will pass away ♪
♪ 他们会怎么说我 ♪
♪ What will they say about me ♪
♪ 当末日来临 ♪
♪ When the end comes ♪
♪ 我知道世上只有小白脸 ♪
♪ I know They'll say ''just a gigolo" ♪
♪ 没有我的生活还在继续 ♪
♪ As life goes on without me ♪
♪ 因为我身边没有别人 ♪
♪ 'Cause I ain't got nobody ♪
♪ 噢 没人关心我 ♪
♪ Oh and just nobody cares for me ♪
♪ 没有人真正关心我 ♪
♪ There's nobody cares for me ♪
♪ 我很悲伤很孤独 ♪
♪ I'm so sad and lonely ♪
♪ 悲伤又孤独 ♪
♪ Sad and lonely sad and lonely ♪
♪ 亲爱的姑娘 ♪
♪ Won't some sweet mama ♪
♪ 来吧和我一起冒险 ♪
♪ Come take a chance with me ♪
♪ 因为我并没有这么坏 ♪
♪ 'Cause I ain't so bad ♪
♪ 一直听着动听的情歌 ♪
♪ And I sing a sweet love song all of the time ♪
♪ 她只会 ♪
♪ She will only be ♪
♪ 啊 啊 她只会 ♪
♪ Oh-oh-only be ♪
♪ 波普迪兹不 兹波（音译） ♪
♪ Bop dee bozee bop zitty bop ♪
♪ 我身边没有别人 ♪
♪ I ain't got nobody ♪
♪ 噢 没有人关心我 ♪
♪ Oh and just nobody cares for me ♪
♪ 没有人关心我 ♪
♪ There's nobody cares for me ♪
♪ Nobody cares for me ♪
你好
Hola.
去哪里？
呃
Um...
拉塔图依 你看到了什么
Ratatouille, what do you got?
三楼走廊没有人
Third floor hallway's clear.
艾布纳呢
Abner?
貌似没有任何车过来
There doesn't seem to be any incoming traffic.
有一只鸟
Bird.
纳努威 把对讲机关掉
Nanaue, stay off the comm.
上校 我瞄准了办公室里唯一一个人
Colonel, I got a clean shot on the only one in the office.
等你发话
Just give the word.
准备开火 三 二
Fire on three, two...
你们在干什么
What are you guys doing?
我... 你 我们来救你了
I... You. We're here to save you.
你们打算...救我？
You were gonna... save me?
营救计划也真的很不错
It was a really good plan, too.
好吧 我可以重新回到里面 然后你们可以完成你们的计划
Well, I can go back inside, and you can still do it.
那倒不必了
That's patronizing.
噢 不 不是那个意思
Yeah, no, it's not...
呃 这个标枪是怎么回事
Uh, what's with the javelin?
我在等待上帝来告诉我答案
I'm waitin' for God to tell me.
我的上帝 对
Jesus Christ. - Yeah.
就是他 或者他们中的任何一个 真的
Or Him. Or any of them, really.
好吧
Okay.
好了 好了
你们两个都还好吗
Are you two all right, yeah?
我很抱歉   -没事的
I'm so sorry. -That's all right.
哈莉奎茵
Harley Quinn.
血腥运动
Bloodsport.
约顿海姆
好吧 谁他妈的把肉馅卷饼都吃了
All right, who ate all the fucking empanadas?
我的很好吃
Mine were very good.
我吃了鸡肉的
I had the chicken.
好了
All right,
说好了 如果我们的任务失败 你会没命
here's the deal. We fail the mission, you die.
如果发现你给我们虚假信息 你会没命
We find out any information you give us is false, you die.
如果发现你有个性化的车牌 你会没命
If we find out you have personalized license plates,you die.
啥？不是的
What? No.
如果你和黑人合不来 你也会没命
If you mismatch blacks, you die.
不会
No.
如果你咳嗽不捂着嘴巴...
If you cough without covering your mouth...
哈莉 最后那三条都不算
Harley. Those last three aren't things.
不过 不用我说你也知道
Although, probably don't need to say this,
这可不是允许你
but that isn't an open invitation
不捂着嘴巴咳嗽的意思啊
for you to cough without covering your mouth.
好了 我们需要你来开那辆面包车
All right, we're gonna need you to drive the minibus,
我们全员藏在车里 躲过大门的守卫
with all of us inside, past the guards at the front gate.
通过大门之后 你就帮我们通过视网膜扫描仪
Once through the gate, we'll use you to get through
但是那儿到处都有监控摄像头啊
There are security cameras everywhere.
都已经准备好了
They're being dealt with.
到时我们就除掉那儿的士兵 进入大楼
We'll neutralize the soldiers there and enter.
进去以后 分成小组行动
Once we're inside, we separate into teams.
看 我在走来走去哎
I am walking back and forth.
行了 你要带着我和捕鼠二代去海星计划的大楼
Okay. You're gonna lead me and Ratcatcher 2
我跟你去 我不信任这家伙
I'm going with you 'cause I don't trust this guy.
不 你得跟我一起
No, no, no, you're coming with me.
我们有弹药的专业知识 在放置炸药的时候用得上
Our munitions expertise are needed
从一楼放炸药一直放到顶楼
starting at the first floor, going all the way to the top.
我们一撤出那里 就把整栋楼炸翻
Once we're clear, we blow the tits off that thing,
然后回家
and go home.
这行动不就等同于自杀吗
This is suicide.
没错 我们就叫自杀小队呀
Well, that's kind of our thing.
没错
Yeah.
这行动太疯狂了
This is insane.
♪ 嘿 ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ 我们之间一定有魔鬼 ♪
♪ Must be a devil between us ♪
♪ 坏女人徘徊在我脑海中 ♪
♪ Or whores in my head ♪
不行
Yeah, no.
♪ 站在我的门前 ♪
♪ Whores at my door ♪
♪ 躺在我的床上 ♪
♪ Whores in my bed ♪
我喜欢下雨
I love the rain.
就像天使射了满天的小蝌蚪
It's like angels are splooging all over us.
对于掩护我们有利
It's good for cover.
对 你说的也对
Yep, that too.
♪ 我一定会死掉 ♪
♪ I will surely die ♪
♪ 我们的生命紧紧连在一起 ♪
♪ We're chained ♪
你这个婊子养
-You son of a bit... -
输入紧急事态密码 快
Input the emergency code. Now!
别傻愣着 快去
Well, go on then!
快去！
身份验证
系统已解锁
他们把这个砸烂了
用不了了！
把功门锤拿过来！
给你
Yo!
好了 波点人
Okay, Pokey.
你拿一个炸弹 你也拿一个炸弹
You get a bomb, you get a bomb.
哈莉和我在二楼跟你们汇合
Harley and I will meet you up
懂吗 好
Yeah? All right.
警告！
大楼里的所有安保人员注意
现有九名入侵者
盖乌斯·格里夫斯博士也在内
找到他们
格杀勿论
行动！
装
在
悍马上！
装
上去！
快
点！
再来！
倒车
再快点！
动作 快点！
再来一次
先生！
撞啊！
天呐 纳努威
God damn it, Nanaue.
停下来
No!
别玩了
Quit bein' a play baby.
和平使者
Peacemaker.
行吧 你做得还挺好看的
It's actually very nice. -
把它放到墙上就行
Just put it against the wall.
跟我一点都不像
It looks nothin' like me.
走 快走
Move. Move it.
这边
This way.
苏亚雷斯总统...
是约顿海姆的
安保部长
打来的电话
喂
Si.
马上出发
Vamonos Vamonos
肮脏的小秘密
上帝啊
Good God.
如果上帝存在
If God existed,
这难道不能证明他一点都不善吗
wouldn't this be proof that he wasn't good at all?
这他妈是什么
What the hell is this?
我以为你在找海星计划
I thought you were looking for Project Starfish.
格里夫斯 你带人来看望我们了 对吗
You've brought us visitors, have you, Grieves?
你是来解救我逃离那个疯子的吗
Have you come to save me from that madman?
他关了我三十年
Thirty years he's kept me here.
折磨了我三十年
Tortured me.
用他残忍的方式虐待我
Had his way with me.
我叫它征服者斯塔罗
I call it Starro the Conqueror.
听起来略带讽刺
That's meant to be derisive.
对不起了老兄
Sorry, old chum.
这两个人是来杀你的
These two are here to kill you.
我可管不了
It's out of my hands.
我们得救他们
We need to help these people.
不可能的 亲爱的 他们是海星手下的死尸
Impossible, dear. They're corpses below those stars.
他们是谁
Who are they?
各个时代里权贵手下的炮灰罢了
The fodder of powerful men through every age.
持不同政见者
Dissidents,
新闻记者
journalists,
政敌
political rivals,
和他们爱的人
and their loved ones.
噢 拜托
Oh, please,
开枪吧 弗莱格
unclutch your fucking pearls, Flag.
我们给同一个老板打工
We serve the same master.
我们是派来阻止你的
We were sent here to stop you.
小朋友
Child,
你的政府不是派你来这
your government didn't send you here
保护世界远离外星科技的
to protect the world from alien technology.
而是派你来收拾他们的烂摊子的
Your government sent you here to cover up their part in it.
你个该死的骗子
You're a goddamn liar.
该死的美国宇航员发现了斯塔罗
American goddamn astronauts found Starro.
一群该死的美国佬花花公子
Yankee-fucking-doodle dandies.
即便冷战结束了
Although the Cold War was ended,
你的政府仍看到了
your government saw the potential
把这个强大野兽武器化的可能性
in weaponizing such a powerful beast,
却又打消了
but banish the thought
在美国国土上进行此类实验的念头
of any such experiments being held on American soil.
你们总是
Your people have always been squeamish
拘泥于道德
about the sacrifices necessary
不肯为科学进步作出必需的牺牲
for scientific advancement.
所以
So,
美国跟柯多马堤斯政府
the United States made a secret deal
进行了一场秘密交易
with the Corto Maltese government
要在这里进行非法实验
to conduct their illegal experiments here
在约顿海姆
in Jotunheim.
他们让我来监督
And they hired me to oversee them.
而现在
And now, because of
因为一场他妈的普通军事政变
a run-of-the-mill fucking military coup,
他们准备毁掉我们三十年的努力
they're gonna destroy 30 years' worth of efforts.
没错
Yeah!
你是这儿真正的受害者
You're the real victim here.
你在这儿干什么 你应该在楼上布置炸药
The hell you doing here? You're supposed to be upstairs
告诉过你我不相信他
I told you I didn't trust him.
记录都在那些电脑里吗
Your records are located in those computers?
上校 你要干什么
Colonel, what are you doing?
我参军是为了报效祖国
I joined the military to serve my country,
不是为了当牵线木偶
not to be its puppet.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
你要把它交给谁
Who are you going to show that to?
媒体 该死的人们应该知道
The press. Goddamn people deserve to know.
我受够了帮他们掩盖那些肮脏的小秘密了
I'm tired of coverin' up their dirty little secrets.
这次这些狗娘养的要完蛋了
This time these sons of bitches
我不能让你那么做 上校
I can't let you do that, Colonel.
你说什么   -非常抱歉
Excuse me? -I'm truly sorry.
沃勒女士让我确保
Miss Waller charged me with makin' sure
这些记录不会离开这栋楼
those records don't leave this building.
当然 我应该知道
Of course, I shoulda known.
沃勒女士总是有备用计划
Waller's always got a backup.
算了吧 哥们 这不是个人恩怨
Come on, man, this isn't personal.
拿枪指着我就是他妈的个人恩怨
Holdin' a gun on me is pretty fucking personal.
怎么回事
What is that?
我需要那个硬盘 上校
I'm gonna need that drive, Colonel.
那些傻瓜引爆得太早了
Those morons set off the explosives too early.
把硬盘给我
Hand over the drive!
我们走 快!
Let's go, come on!
他们用孩子做实验
They experimented on children.
没有人说他们做的是对的
No one is sayin' what they did was right.
他们拿孩子来做实验
They experimented on children!
那些信息传出去
That information gets out,
会引发国际事件
it causes an international incident!
维持和平不惜任何代价
Keepin' the peace is worth any price,
包括像你这样的英雄的生命 上校
including the life of a hero like yours, sir,
所以拜托
so please...
别逼我
don't make me do this.
你们这些人干了什么
What have you people done?
塞巴斯蒂安 过来
Sebastian, come!
好 我们要冷静
Okay, we gotta calm down.
我们...我们来谈谈
Let's all just... Let's talk about this.
我明白你这么做的原因
I understand where you're coming from.
我越界了
I crossed a line.
好吧 我做得太过了
Okay, I crossed a line!
我知道自己做得太过了 我会改的
I realize that, but I'm ready to change.
我会改的
I am ready to change.
我不是故意要伤害你
And I didn't mean to hurt you...
你个混蛋
You motherfucker.
和平使者
Peacemaker.
真是笑话
What a joke.
克利欧
Cleo.
把硬盘还给我
Give me back the drive.
我告诉过你那些信息不能泄露 操
I told you that information can't get out. Fuck!
好的 好 那就毁掉这个硬盘
So, okay, okay, destroy the hard drive.
为什么要杀我?
Why kill me?
因为我办事严谨
Because I'm thorough.
噢 我
-Oh, my...
抱歉 孩子
Sorry, kid.
不 不要
No, no...
八分钟前
好了 军队来了
All right, troops are coming.
装完这一层 还剩下九层 我们走
This floor, and then nine floors left. Let's go!
快点
Come on!
新的傻朋友
New dumb friends.
喔 袋子漏了 等下
Aw, fizzle sticks. Hold on.
你们的眼睛和耳朵还好使吗
Has anyone got eyes or ears on any more?
他们杀了弥尔顿
They killed Milton!
弥尔顿还跟着我们呢
Milton was still with us?
不然你以为他在哪?   -我哪知道
Where'd you think he was? - I don't know.
我以为他待在车里
I thought he stayed back with the bus.
弥尔顿刚才想干嘛？
What was Milton gonna do?
他在帮我们
He was helping us!
谁是弥尔顿 什么
-Who's Milton? -What?
我不记得有谁叫弥尔顿
I don't remember any Milton.
操 他一直都跟着我们啊
Fuck! He has been with us the whole time.
有个叫弥尔顿的人一直都跟我们一起吗？
Somebody named Milton has been with us
是的
Yes!
不是吧 要是有个叫弥尔顿的人跟着我们
I don't think so. I think I would've noticed
我会注意到的
if a guy named Milton's been with us.
这个名字可不常见
It's not a very common name.
我从没见过叫弥尔顿的人
I don't think I've ever even met Milton.
你现在是在找事儿吗？
Are you messing around right now?
他是个非常好的人
He was a really nice guy,
为了帮我们 还牺牲了自己
and he sacrificed himself to help us.
现在看看他
And now look at him.
他死了
He's dead.
喔 那个人啊 弥尔顿 弥尔顿
Oh, that guy! Milton, Milton.
你什么时候跟弥尔顿暗生情愫了
So, when did this great love affair with Milton start?
我一开始就挺喜欢他 好吗
I liked him from the beginning, okay?
我只是什么都没说 直到
I just didn't say anything until...
不
No!
哈莉 帮帮我们
Harley! Give us a hand!
开火...
快开火！
嘿
Hey!
前进 前进
Vamos. Vamos.
快点离开这，快点！
快点！
棒
Oh!
真是操蛋了
Oh, fuck, fuck.
该死的
Oh, fuck off!
哦豁
-Oh. -
孩子 对不住了
Sorry, kid.
不 不要
No, no, no.
怎么会这样
How?
我的子弹更小
Smaller bullets.
他杀了弗莱格上校
He killed Colonel Flag.
上校想把这个交给媒体
He wanted to share this with the press.
这里面有美国政府
It's proof the American government
参加海星计划的证据
was behind Project Starfish the whole time.
哇哦 哇哦
Whoa. Whoa.
那东西想跑出来
I think it's trying to get out.
什么东西?  -斯塔罗
What? -Starro the...
哇哦
Whoa.
自杀小队
大战
征服者斯塔罗
这他妈什么情况？
开火！
快开火！
快捂住脸!
Cover your faces!
好的
Si.
苏亚雷斯死了
那么我现在是总统了
将军们
我们
柯多马堤斯人民
现在接管政府
乖乖退位吧
哇哦 这他妈是什么
-Whoa. -What the fuck is that?
呃 伙计们
Uh... Hey, guys?
卧槽 这些人
Oh, shit, there's...
这座城市 属于我
This city is mine.
沃勒女士 好像有信号了
Uh, Miss Waller, I think the feed is back up.
我的天 沃勒女士
Oh, my God, Miss Waller!
这儿有个吓死人的大怪物
We've got a freaking kaiju up in this shit!
X特遣队 收到请回复
Task force X, come in.
听得见吗
Are you there?
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
刚刚你们爆破的大楼里面
Whatever signal jammers
应该有一台信号干扰机
were blocking our communications
之前一直在影响我们的通信
must have been in the building you just demolished.
对 我们这儿有点小麻烦 沃勒
Yeah, well, we've got a mite issue over here, Waller.
沃勒女士 是海星计划
It's Project Starfish, Miss Waller.
现在这只巨大的海星正在向着市中心进发
It's headed towards the city, and I think it wants
我觉得他想吃更多的人
to feed on as many people as it can.
这不归我们管
Not our problem.
你们的任务就是摧毁约顿海姆和里面的数据
If you've destroyed Jotunheim and the records within,
其他的都不在你们的管辖范围内
you've achieved the objective.
柯多马堤斯已经解除和美国的合作关系了
Corto Maltese is no longer a U.S. ally.
况且对于白宫来说
If anything, the White House will consider
敌国的沦陷
fomenting disruption in a hostile nation
也算是促进了本国的发展
a positive development.
听到她说的了吗
You heard what she said.
操
Fuck.
血腥运动离队了
Bloodsport is off mission.
怎么回事
What the...
她会把你碎尸万段的
She'll kill you, you know.
那是她的事
That's her business.
我就知道塞巴斯蒂安对你有好感是有原因的
I knew Sebastian sensed good in you for a reason.
让那只臭老鼠离我远点
Just keep that fucking rat away from me.
捕鼠者也离开任务了
Ratcatcher is also off mission.
血腥运动 捕鼠者
Bloodsport, Ratcatcher,
快给我回去
turn around.
你们要去哪 朋友们
Where go, friends?
纳努威
Nanaue!
我终于知道我是为了什么才拿着标枪了
I know what I'm carrying the javelin for.
马上回去 科瑞尔
Krill, turn around now!
都他妈给我回去 操
Turn back now, God damn it!
把它打开 沃勒女士
-Open it. -Miss Waller...
快给我打开
Open it!
你们在干什么 X特遣队
What are you doing, Task Force X?
操
Fuck!
都他妈给我转身回去 该死的
Turn around now, God damn it!
你们这群耳朵聋了的废物
You dumb pieces of shit!
操你妈
Motherfuckers!
操 这他妈是给你们的最后一次警告
God damn it, Task Force X, this is your last
X特遣队
motherfucking warning!
我的天呐 你他妈的做了什么
Oh, my God! What the fuck did you do?
看看这些人们 约翰
All those people, John.
还有小孩
Little kids.
X特遣队 那个怪物正在去往主街
Task Force X, the creature is headed to Calle Principal.
避开梅德拉诺大道
Avoid Avenida Medrano.
那里有一大群人都被感染了   -上帝啊
There is a swarm of infected. - Jesus.
你们直接从阿奎罗街过去
So, your clearest path is Calle Aguero.
回去盯着你的卫星去 戴尔 你个蠢蛋
Get on the satellite, Dale, you fucking dickhead!
好的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
嗯？
Huh?
哈莉 去高处!
Harley, take the high ground!
纳努威 怪物 好吃
Nanaue! Monster is nom nom!
怪物 好吃？
Monster nom nom?
是的
Yes!
艾布纳 你看到那是谁了吗
Abner, do you see who that is?
谁？
Huh?
那是你妈！
It's your mom!
我是超级英雄
I'm a superhero!
我是他妈的超级...
I'm a motherfucking super...
天呐
God!
不 不要
No! No!
噢 不
Oh, no...
这座城市
This city
是我的
is mine!
这座城市不属于你
This city isn't yours.
这座城市也不属于我们
This city isn't ours.
这座城市是它们的
This city is theirs.
噢 天
Oh, hell.
为什么是老鼠呢 爸爸
Why rats, Papa?
在所有生物中老鼠的地位最低
Rats are the lowliest and most despised
也是最受鄙视的 宝贝
of all creatures, my love.
如果它们都有目标
If they have purpose,
我们也该有
so do we all.
我也曾幸福过
I was happy,
自由漂浮 仰望星空
floating, staring at the stars.
今天一群逃犯
A group of escaped convicts
在一个叫柯多马堤斯的小岛国上
saved a city of millions
拯救了一座人口百万的城市
on the small island nation of Corto Maltese today.
那是我爸爸
That's my dad.
突发新闻
外星怪物战争导致政治动荡
在得到他们的帮助后
Because of these people,
柯多马堤斯将举行九十年以来的
Corto Maltese will have free democratic elections
柯多马堤斯政变
突发新闻
首次自由民主选举
for the first time in 90 years.
柯多马堤斯万岁
Viva Corto Maltese!
突发新闻
柯多马堤斯政变
柯多马堤斯万岁！柯多
Viva Corto Maltese! Viva...
那是我爸爸   -...万岁！柯多
That's my dad. -...Corto Maltese! Viva...
嗯
Yeah.
对
这只是硬盘内容的一小部分
Oh, that's just a taste of what's on that drive.
我已经上传到某个安全服务器了
I've uploaded it all to a secure server.
如果你杀了我的队友 无论是谁
Now, if you kill any one of us,
或者我女儿进了监狱
or my daughter ever sees the inside of a prison,
这些内容就会将公之于众
it goes public.
要是我们都重获自由
If we all go free,
这些秘密就可以永不见天日
it never has to see the light of day.
我说过你是当领导的料 迪布瓦
I told you I'd make you a leader, DuBois.
一言为定
You got a deal.
纳努威
Nanaue.
我知道弗莱格想把硬盘给媒体
Look, I know Flag wanted to give the drive to the press,
但我们刚救下这座城市
but we just saved a whole bloody city.
鱼和熊掌不可兼得
We can't have it all.
弗莱格是我的朋友
Flag was my friend.
也是我朋友
Mine too.
我朋友并不多
And I haven't got many of those.
我可以做你的朋友 弥尔顿
I could be your friend, Milton.
我不叫弥尔顿
Not my name.
什么
What?
你说什么呢 我们不是刚聊过
What are you talkin' about? We just had a conversation
讲了差不多三个小时 讨论你为什么叫弥尔顿
for, like, three hours about how your name is Milton.
没有的事
Didn't.
绝对有
Yes, we did.
没有 接我们的人来了
No. Our ride's here.
好吃吗
Nom nom?
你认真的吗
Really?
这种时候你就想着吃
That is what you're thinkin' about right now?
不 那这个好吃吗
No. That nom nom though.
不 那个不好吃
No, it's not nom nom.
不
No!
♪ 我不在乎是否拥有一辆梦想中的豪车 ♪
♪ I don't care about a fancy car ♪
♪ 除非它能将我带向你 ♪
♪ Unless it's taking me to you ♪
♪ 我也不在乎你我之间相隔多远 ♪
♪ And I don't care about how far you are ♪
♪ 你也知道我总是会克服艰难险阻，为了你 ♪
♪ You know I'll always come through for you ♪
♪ 我不想错过了又一个生日派对 ♪
♪ I don't wanna miss another birthday party ♪
♪ 或是你的一生中的任何一天♪
♪ Or any day in between ♪
♪ 我想象着我们老去依旧紧握彼此的手 ♪
♪ I picture us holding hands when we're older ♪
♪ 尽管这可能只是一场梦 ♪
♪ Though it's probably just a dream ♪
♪ 生活是如此的糟糕 ♪
♪ 'Cause life is so busted ♪
♪ 人生是如此的糟糕 ♪
♪ Life is so busted ♪
♪ 我的车简直弱爆了 ♪
♪ My car is so busted ♪
♪ 人生啊 和我一样的失败 ♪
♪ Life I'm so busted ♪
♪ 但我也想得到你的爱，被你爱着 ♪
♪ And I just wanted to be loved by you, by you ♪
♪ 我只是想被你关心着，宠爱着 ♪
♪ I just wanted to be loved by you, by you ♪
♪ 我只想被你喜欢，被你爱 ♪
全员集结
X特遣队
字幕制作：猫和老鼠
字幕参考：远鉴字幕组
♪ 天空里再次烟雾弥漫 ♪
♪ There's smoke in the sky again ♪
♪ 所以我再次兴奋不已 ♪
♪ So I'm gettin' high again ♪
♪ 再一次享受极致的乐趣 ♪
♪ Take another hit to the diaphragm ♪
♪ 我从未画过示意图 ♪
♪ I never drew the diagram ♪
♪ 如何应对重重危机 ♪
♪ How to deal with this shit ♪
♪ 所以我再次偷窃欺骗 ♪
♪ So I steal and lie again woah ♪
♪ 你是我的梦想 你是我的梦魇 ♪
♪ You're my dream you're my nightmare ♪
♪ 人生布满荆棘 毫无公平可言 ♪
♪ Life is a bitch she don't fight fair ♪
♪ 将你留在原地 ♪
♪ Leave you right there ♪
♪ 我希望你注意到我万念俱灰 ♪
♪ I was hopin' that you'd notice my despair ♪
♪ 逃避痛苦 我毫不在乎 ♪
♪ Run away from the pain I don't care 'cause ♪
♪ 首先 他们煽动暴力 ♪
♪ First they incite the violence ♪
♪ 转过身去 他们让一切变得万籁俱寂 ♪
♪ Turn around and then they invite the silence ♪
♪ 焚烧殆尽 我想我需要一些指引 ♪
♪ Burn it down and I think I need some guidance ♪
♪ 孩子们毫无获胜的机会 ♪
♪ The kids don't stand a chance ♪
♪ No the kids don't stand a chance ♪
♪ 父辈面临的难题卷土重来 ♪
♪ Old man trouble back again ♪
♪ 搅乱我的计划 ♪
♪ Fcukin' up my plans like oh no oh no ♪
♪ 我再次回到暗无天日的世界 ♪
♪ I'm back to the black again ♪
♪ 再次变得糟糕透顶 ♪
♪ Gettin' fcuked up again oh no oh no ♪
♪ 父辈面临的难题卷土重来 ♪
♪ Old man trouble back again ♪
♪ 以为我占领上风 ♪
♪ Thought I had the upper hand oh no oh no ♪
♪ 我再次回到暗无天日的世界 ♪
♪ I'm back to the black again ♪
♪ 再次变得糟糕透顶 ♪
♪ Gettin' fucked up again oh no oh no ♪
♪ 我沦陷在烟酒当中 ♪
♪ Now I drink, smoke ♪
♪ 无论如何 我都是个笑话 ♪
♪ Whatever you selling I'm a sick joke ♪
♪ 领导罪业深重 我无力反抗 ♪
♪ My president's a felon and I can't cope ♪
♪ 我痛并快乐着 ♪
♪ I'm in love with the pain ♪
♪ 我让朋友躲灾避难 ♪
♪ So I stick Poke with my kinfolk ♪
♪ 让我沉迷于烟酒 ♪
♪ Gimme drink, smoke ♪
♪ 无论如何 我都是个笑话 ♪
♪ Whatever you selling I'm a sick joke ♪
♪ 领导罪业深重 我无力反抗 ♪
♪ My president's a felon and I can't cope ♪
♪ 我痛并快乐着 ♪
♪ I'm in love with the pain ♪
♪ 我们挑战极限 这样很酷 ♪
♪ We taking on the system 'cause it broke, whoo ♪
♪ 哦 不！ ♪
♪ Oh, no! ♪
♪ 父辈面临的难题卷土重来 ♪
♪ Old man trouble back again ♪
♪ 搅乱我的计划 ♪
♪ Fucking up my plans like oh no oh no ♪
♪ 我再次回到暗无天日的世界 ♪
♪ I'm back to the black again ♪
♪ 再次变得糟糕透顶 ♪
♪ Gettin' fucked up again oh no oh no ♪
♪ 父辈面临的难题卷土重来 ♪
♪ Old man trouble back again ♪
♪ 以为我占领上风 ♪
♪ Thought I had the upper hand oh no oh no ♪
♪ 我再次回到暗无天日的世界 ♪
♪ I'm back to the black again ♪
♪ 再次变得糟糕透顶 ♪
♪ Gettin' fcuked up again oh no oh no ♪
字幕制作：猫和老鼠
字幕参考：远鉴字幕组
X特遣队
全员集结
他们说在废墟里找到了他
Said they found him in the rubble.
当时还有心跳 他们都震惊了
They were shocked his heart was still beating.
我不确定把他运回来
I wasn't certain how safe it was,
是否安全
shipping him back here.
但还好 他很坚强
But, if anything, he's shown he's resilient.
得做手术
It'll take some surgery,
但我们会让他恢复如常
but eventually we'll get him back up to speed.
你知道这是报复吧
You realize this is revenge, right?
沃勒知道我们背叛了她
Waller knows we double-crossed her,
她开始报复我们了
and she's getting back at us
让我们负责这个混蛋
by saddling us with this douchebag.
是啊
Yep.
我听说他在柯多马堤斯是个英雄
I heard he was sort of a hero down in Corto Maltese.
你是这么听说的吗 才不是这样
Oh, is that what you heard? Because not quite.
你们想让他做什么
What do you guys want him for?
救一救这该死的世界就行
Just to save the fucking world, that's all.
亚 特 拉 斯 娱 乐 公
司
旗下公司
媒体
华纳